(Sheldon:)Exactly.
(Amy:)Well, I wouldn't want you
to starve to death, so...
(Amy:)...here's an eggplant.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Amy:)You know, some people
believe that Buridan
(Amy:)was plagiarizing Aristotle.
(Sheldon:)Really?
(Leonard:)Although,
(Amy:)in Aristotle's example,
(Amy:)he proposed an equally
hungry and thirsty man
(Amy:)caught between food and drink.
(Sheldon:)Huh.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, I wonder if that's related
(Sheldon:)to the 12th century
Persian philosopher,
(Sheldon:)Al-Ghazali
(Sheldon:)and his story of a man
(Sheldon:)caught between two dates.
(Amy:)Are you suggesting Al-Ghazali
was Aristotelian?
'Cause if anything,
he was anti-Aristotelian.
(Amy:)Al-Ghazali was
anti-Aristotelian?
(Sheldon:)Boy, you think you know a guy.
(Leonard:)Okay.
(Penny:)Open your eyes and
see your new room.
(Penny:)Wow.
I-I know I went
a little overboard.
(Penny:)We can always
dial it back.
(Leonard:)No, no, no, no, no,
it's-it's important to me
(Leonard:)that you have
the bedroom you want.
(Penny:)Oh, that means so
much. I love you.
(Leonard:)I love you, too.
(Leonard:)Just hiding some stuff in
your closet, don't tell Penny.